https://texastreats.com/privacy-policy-2/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main contentTexas Treats (texastreats.com) is committed to maintaining robust privacy protections for its users.  Our Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our website.Information We Collect We collect non-personal information and personal information.Non-personal information includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as anonymous usage data, general demographic information we may collect, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you submit and number of clicks.Personal Information includes only your email, which you submit to us through the registration process at the website.Information collected via TechnologyTo activate the service you do not need to submit any personal Information other than your email address.To use the service thereafter, you do not need to submit further personal information.However, in an effort to improve the quality of the service, we track information provided to us by your browser or by our software application when you view or use the Texas Treats website, such as the website you came from (known as the “referring URL”), the type of browser you use, the device from which you connected to the website, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you.We track this information using cookies, or small text files which include an anonymous unique identifier.  Cookies are sent to a user’s browser from our servers and are stored on the user’s computer hard drive.Sending a cookie to a user’s browser enables us to collect non-personal information about that user and keep a record of the user’s preferences when utilizing our services, both on an individual and aggregate basis.  For example, Texas Treats may use cookies to collect the following information:Pages visitedProducts added to shopping cartTime on the siteTexas Treats may use both persistent and session cookies; persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your session and until you delete them, while session cookies expire when you close your browser.  For example, we store a persistent cookie to track items in your shopping cart during your visit.Information you provide us by registering for an accountIn addition to the information provided automatically by your browser when you visit the website, to become a subscriber to the website you will need to create a personal profile.You can create a profile by registering with the website and entering your email address, and creating a user name and a password.By registering, you are authorizing us to collect, store and use your email address in accordance with this Privacy Policy.Personal InformationExcept as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise share for marketing purposes your personal information with third parties without your consent.We do share personal information with vendors who are performing services for the Texas Treats, such as the servers for our email communications who are provided access to user’s email address for purposes of sending emails from us.Those vendors use your personal information only at our direction and in accordance with our Privacy Policy.In general, the Personal Information you provide to us is used to help us communicate with you.  For example, we use Personal Information to contact users in response to questions, solicit feedback from users, provide technical support, and inform users about promotional offers.Non Personal InformationIn general, we use non-personal information to help us improve the website and customize the user experience.  We also aggregate non-personal information in order to track trends and analyze use patterns on the webite.This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of non-personal information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such non-personal information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our discretion.In the event we undergo a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your personal information may be among the assets transferred.You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of our assets may continue to process your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.If our information practices change at any time in the future, we will post the policy changes to the website so that you may opt out of the new information practices.We suggest that you check the website periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used.How We Protect InformationWe implement security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.Your account is protected by your account password and we urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe by not disclosing your password and by logging out of your account after each use.We further protect your information from potential security breaches by implementing certain technological security measures including encryption, firewalls and secure socket layer technology.However, these measures do not guarantee that your information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.By using our website, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.Your Rights in Regard to Your Personal Information You have the right at any time to prevent us from contacting you for marketing purposes.When we send a promotional communication to a user, the user can opt out of further promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in each promotional e-mail.You can also indicate that you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us in the “Settings” section of the website.Please note that notwithstanding the promotional preferences you indicate by either unsubscribing or opting out in the Settings section of the website, we may continue to send you administrative emails including, for example, periodic updates to our Privacy Policy.Links to Other Websites As part of the Service, we may provide links to or compatibility with other websites or applications.However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those websites or the information or content they contain.This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site and the Service.Therefore, this Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of a third party website accessed by selecting a link on our Site or via our Service.To the extent that you access or use the Service through or on another website or application, then the privacy policy of that other website or application will apply to your access or use of that site or application.We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of other websites before proceeding to use them.Changes to Our Privacy Policy The Company reserves the right to change this policy and our Terms of Service at any time.We will notify you of significant changes to our Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.Significant changes will go into effect 30 days following such notification.  Non-material changes or clarifications will take effect immediately.You should periodically check the Site and this privacy page for updates.Contact Us If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this website, please contact us here.Gift Baskets & Gourmet Foods Dismiss
